- 嘿     - 嘿
- Hey.         - Hey.
- 摩妮卡呢？ - 她在家…
- Where's Mon?     - She's at home...
帮瑞秋今晚的生日派对做布置
putting up decorations for Rachel's birthday party tonight.
- 你不用帮忙吗？ - 我有试过…
- And you're not helping?     - I tried...
但是很明显地 用氦语音唱 《我会活下去》并没有帮助
but apparently singing "I Will Survive" in a helium voice, not helping.
- 嘿 你们好   - 嘿
- Hey, you guys.     - Hey.
祝你生…
Happy birth...
别说那么大声 阿甘会过来抱我的
Shh. Don't say that loud. Gunther's gonna want to hug me.
好消息 我们终于找到保姆了
Uh, good news, everyone. We finally found a nanny.
- 这位是莫莉 莫莉 钱德 乔伊   - 嗨
- This is Molly. Molly, Chandler, Joey.     - Hi.
有人有点不高兴喔
Ooh, somebody's getting a little fussy.
你说的没错 我就是不高兴 我已经等饼干等了七分钟了
You're damn right I am. I've been waiting for a cookie for seven minutes.
好了 我想我带她出去好了
Okay. You know what, I'm just gonna take her outside.
- 不 你留下来 我去   - 好的 谢谢
- No, you stay. I'll do it.     - Okay. Thank you.
- 很高兴认识你们   - 是啊 我们也是
- Nice to meet you guys.     - Yeah, you too.
- 哇 莫莉真的很不错   - 是啊
- Wow, Molly's just great.     - Yeah.
是啊 真棒 请了个辣保姆
Yes, bravo on the hot nanny.
- 什么？你真的觉得她很辣吗？ - 你看不出来吗？
- What? You really think she's hot?     - Are you kidding?
如果我未婚 她现在就在拒绝我了
If I wasn't married, she'd be rejecting me right now.
乔伊？
Joey?
觉得她怎样？
How do you think she's doing?
我是唯一不觉得她练的吗？罗斯？
Am I the only one that doesn't think she's hot? Ross?
- 我觉得她不算是没有魅力 但是…   - 没错
- Ah, I mean, she's not unattractive, but...     - Right.
但是算辣吗？
but hot? Ah...
谢谢你
Thank you. Ha, ha.
瑞秋走了 说吧
Now that Rachel's gone?
她真辣 我昨晚是哭着入睡的
So hot, I cried myself to sleep last night.
嘿 麦克 秘鲁的首都是哪呢？
Hey, Mike, what's the capital of Peru?
- 利马   - 不是
- Lima.     - No.
是V开头X结尾的字
It starts with a V and ends with an X.
然后最好中间有T跟O
And hopefully with a T-O in the middle.
我仔细想想之后 我想秘鲁的首都 应该叫做"VTOX"
You know, come to think of it, the capital of Peru is "Vtox."
- 喔 天啊   - 怎么了？
- Oh, God!     - What?
好了 我不想要吓坏你
Okay. I don't want to freak you out or anything...
但是我刚才在柜子里看到一只老鼠
but I just saw a rat in your cupboard.
喔 是喔 那是霸柏
Oh, yeah. No, that's Bob.
是你的宠物鼠吗？
Well, he's your pet rat?
不太算是 只是偶尔会来拜访
Well, not so much a pet as, you know, an occasional visitor...
我有时候会喂他有点像圣诞老公公
who I put food out for. You know, kind of like Santa.
除了圣诞老公公 不会在饼干盘里便便以外
Except Santa doesn't poop on the plate of cookies.
你不能在公寓里养老鼠 那很不卫生的
You can't keep a rat in your apartment. They're extremely unsanitary.
我是说 他们可能会 传染细螺旋体病或是汉他病毒
I mean, they transmit leptospirosis and hantavirus.
- 那是什么？ - 我不知道
- What are those?     - I don't know...
但是听起来可不像是水疗吧
but they don't sound like spa treatments.
- 你必须要处理掉他   - 好啦
- You have to get rid of it.     - Okay, fine.
如果你这么在乎 我会处理掉霸柏的
If it means that much to you, I'll get rid of Bob.
谢谢你
Thank you.
真奇怪 你觉得他很恶心 却又在吃他的饼干
It's so weird you think he's so gross, yet you're willing to eat his crackers.
- 哈罗   - 哈罗
- Hello.     - Hello.
盖文 我想再次跟你道谢
Gavin, I just want to say thank you again...
谢谢昨天帮我照顾艾玛
for watching Emma yesterday during the presentation.
我真的需要跟你道歉
I really owe you an apology.
- 道什么歉？ - 当我们第一次见面时 你知道的…
- For what?     - When we first met, you know...
我以为你是自负 高仿又讨人厌的人
I thought you were pompous and arrogant and obnoxious.
这是你的第一个对不起吗？
Is this your first apology?
不 我是说第一印象 通常不是很重要的
No, I just mean, you know, first impressions don't mean anything.
而我认为你是个好男人 很抱歉我错看了你
And I think you're a really good guy. And I'm sorry that I misjudged you.
- 早安   - 哈罗
- Morning.     - Hello.
但是你知道吗？ 新的一天 新的开始
But you know what? Hey, new day, new leaf.
我只是真的很高兴…
I am just really, really happy...
我很抱歉 很明显地 海瑟的屁股 有更重要的事要对你说
I'm sorry. Obviously, Heather's ass has something more important to say...
我先让它说完好了
so I'll just wait till it's finished.
- 什么？ - 我正在跟你道歉…
- What?     - I was giving you an apology...
而你一直在打量她
and you were totally checking her out.
我没有 我是在时装业工作 我只是在看她的裙子
I wasn't checking her out. I'm in fashion. I was looking at her skirt.
还是裤子呢？我并没有看清楚 屁股以下的部位
Or was it pants? I didn't really see what happened below the ass area.
哇 你真的是… 你真是小人
Wow, you are really... You're really a creep.
就算我是在看她 你又在乎什么呢？
What do you even care if I was looking at her?
你是在忌妒吗？
Are you jealous?
喔 是啊 我好忌妒
Oh, yeah. I'm jealous.
"喔 盖文 拜托请看看我的屁股"
"Oh, Gavin. Please, please look at my ass."
不要看我的屁股
Stop looking at my ass.
我只是认为这样的行为是不妥的
I mean, I just think you are totally inappropriate. Okay?
这是工作场所 她是你下属
This is a work environment. She's your subordinate.
但是你跟你前助理泰格上床 却是可以的
But it was okay when you slept with your old assistant, Tag?
那是不一样的事 因为两个原因
That is totally different for two reasons.
一 我不知道你知道这件事
One, I didn't know that you knew that.
二 我不是盯着他屁股看的小人
And two, I wasn't some creep staring at his ass.
我们有很深入 有意义的交往
We had a... We had a deep, meaningful relationship.
泰格姓什么？
Huh. What was Tag's last name?
姓…
It was...
喔 我的天
Oh, my God.
他没有姓
He didn't have a last name.
只是叫秦格而已 你知道的 就像雪儿或是…
It was just Tag, you know, like Cher or...
摩西一样
you know, Moses.
但是那是很深入 有意义的交柱
But it was a deep, meaningful relationship.
你知道吗？我对你的第一印象 完全正确
You know what? My first impression of you was absolutely right.
你很高傲 你很自负 摩根 摩根
You are arrogant. You are pompous. Morgan! Morgan!
- 泰格姓摩根   - 是琼斯
- Tag's last name was Morgan! Ha!     - It was Jones.
你是谁啊？他男朋友吗？
What are you, his boyfriend?
(中央咖啡厅)
天啊 我希望我有个像你一样的保姆
Man, I wish I had a nanny like you.
你是说在你小时候吗？
You mean when you were a baby?
当然
Sure.
你可不可以别再盯着她看？
Would you stop staring at her?
我没有盯着
I wasn't staring.
我是斜眼瞄着
I was leering.
她又什么了不起的呢？
What's the big deal with her?
或许她有很抢眼的魅力
Maybe she's attractive in an obvious kind of way.
是啊 很抢眼的魅力最糟糕了
Yeah, obvious beauty's the worst.
你知道的 当它就显现在你面前时
You know, when it's right there in your face.
我比较喜欢渐渐去发掘一个人的魅力
Me, I like to have to work to find someone attractive.
让我感觉像是我辛苦得来的
Makes me feel like I earned it.
看起来乔伊好像跟她处得不错
Looks like Joey's doing all right with her.
嘿 你们两个这次愿意退让出…
Yeah. Hey, that was nice of you guys to back off...
让乔伊去泡她 真是好心
and let Joey get the girl for once.
- 我要带她回去了   - 好的 我下班之后就回去
- I'm gonna take her to the apartment.     - Okay, I'll be home right after work.
- 好的   - 好的 艾玛再见
- Okay.     - Okay, bye, Emma-wemma-demma.
我爱你
I lovey-wovey-dove you.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye.     - Bye.
他们推派我来跟你说 你模仿婴儿说话的事
They've elected me to talk to you about the baby talk.
大家不是很喜欢
It's not so good.
我觉得挺可爱的
I think it's sweet.
再见 艾玛
Bye, Emma-wemma!
嘿 乔伊 关于莫莉 我希望你不要去动她
Hey, listen, Joey. About Molly, I would really prefer if you didn't go after her.
为什么不行？
Why not?
因为我们花了好几个月才找到好保姆
Because it took months to find a good nanny.
而我不希望有任何事情让她离开
And I wouldn't want anything to, you know, drive her away.
所以你认为我只会跟她上床…
So you think I'm just gonna sleep with her...
之后就不再打电话给她 让一切都变得很尴尬吗？
and never call her again, and things are gonna get uncomfortable?
是啊 听起来好像也对
Yeah, that sounds about right.
别这样 外面到处都是女人
Come on, there are plenty of other women out there, okay?
忘了她好吗？她不是你可以要的
Just forget about her, okay? She's off-limits.
天啊 你为什么要这样说呢？
Oh, man. What'd you have to go and say that for?
你这样说之后 我就更想要她了
Now that you told me I can't have her, makes me want her even more!
- 你还是小孩啊？ - 是的
- What are you, a child?     - Yes.
听着 乔伊 别这样 为了我 拜托
Look, Joey, come on now. For me, please.
把你的性能量转移到别人身上
Just try to focus your sexual energy on someone else.
好啦
Fine.
带我回家吧
Take me home.
- 嘿 麦克   - 嘿 菲比
- Hey, Mikey.     - Hey, Pheeb.
- 你在做什么呢？ - 放捕鼠器
- What are you doing?     - Setting rattraps.
- 要杀霸柏吗？ - 不是 只是测试一下他脖子有多硬
- To kill Bob?     - No. No, to test his neck strength.
不 我不想杀死他 我以为我们要活抓他
But no, I don't want to kill him. I thought we were gonna capture him...
然后到乡下把他放生
and, you know, set him free in the countryside...
让他可以认识友善的负鼠
where he could meet a friendly possum...
还有爱说笑的猫头鹰
and a wisecracking owl.
好了 我把捕鼠器丢掉
Okay, okay. I'll throw away the traps.
好 我会找到霸柏 我会抓到他的
All right, I'll find Bob. I'll get him.
霸柏？霸柏？
Bob? Bob?
陈霸柏？
Robert?
等等 我听到他的声音了
Wait, I think I hear him.
天啊 霸柏生小孩了 霸柏当妈妈了
Oh, my God! Bob had babies! Bob's a mom!
我们得替她改名字了
We'll have to think of a new name.
我不知道 我喜欢"霸柏"当女生名字
Oh, I don't know, I kind of like "Bob" for a girl.
不不 我是说我不确定我们…
No, no. I mean, I'm not sure that we...
天啊 我们杀了霸柏吗？
Oh, my God. We killed Bob?
或许不是霸柏 或许只是另一只老鼠
Well, maybe it wasn't Bob. Maybe it was a mouse.
苏西？
Susie?
怎么了？
What's up?
真的 老兄 三年了
Seriously, dude. Three years ago.
听着 你可以帮我一个忙吗？ 我今天要出去
Listen, can you do me a favor? I'm gonna be out today.
你可以帮我看着乔伊…
Can you keep an eye on Joey...
确保他跟莫莉之间不会出事吗？
make sure nothing happens between him and Molly?
- 你不相信他吗？ - 嗯 不相信
- You don't trust him?     - Well, no.
昨晚有个听起来 很像乔伊的女人打电话来…
Some woman who sounded a lot like Joey called earlier...
要找她那个叫做"辣保姆"的女儿
and asked for her daughter, uh, the "hot nanny."
你打算让我长期干预他们吗？
Is this really your long-term plan, for me to run interference?
我可能随时都会找到工作的
Because I could get a job any day now.
你在职场上可真是炙手可热
You do appear right on the cusp of something.
听着 拜托 我确定他一两星期就会没兴趣了
Look, come on, man. I'm sure he'll lose interest in a week or two...
但是现在 你可以帮我这个忙吗？
but for now, could you please just do this for me?
好啦 但是如果失败可别怪我喔
Fine, but don't blame me if it doesn't work.
因为你也了解 乔伊一旦下定决心…
Because you know once Joey sets his mind on something...
无论如何 他都会把她搞上手的
more often than not, he's going to have sex with it.
那我们得要做点什么 不是吗？
Well, I mean, we've gotta do something. Okay?
像她那样的保姆是不会 凭空出现在树上的
Nannies like her don't grow on trees.
- 在想像那棵树吗？ - 是的 没错
- Picturing that tree?     - I am, yes.
你要去哪？乔伊
Where you going, Joe?
去散步
For a walk.
我也去好吗？
Oh, you mind if I join you?
事实上 我想要一个人去 我真的需要理清一些想法
Actually, uh, I'd rather be alone. You know, I really need to organize my thoughts.
一些想法？
Your thoughts?
复数的？
Plural?
好啦 我只有一个想法
All right, fine. I only have one thought.
就是关于那个辣保姆 我必须见到她
It's about the hot nanny. I gotta see her.
- 恐怕我不能让你去 乔伊   - 你是说我不能见她？
- I'm afraid I can't let you do that, Joe.     - Now you're telling me I can't see her?
你是在害死我 她是禁果 这就像…
You guys are killing me. She's forbidden fruit. It's like, like...
她是公主而我是马僮
Like she's the princess and I'm the stable boy.
为什么你要这样？
Why are you doing this, huh?
是不是罗斯要你别让我过去的呢？
Did Ross tell you not to let me go over there?
没错 事实上就是 所以我不能让你过去
Yes, as a matter of fact, he did. So I can't let you go.
有趣 现在出现阻碍了
Huh. Interesting. Now there are obstacles.
辣保姆跟我一起抵抗全世界
Hot nanny and me against the world.
这就像伟大的爱情小说
This is the stuff great novels are made of.
- 伟大的爱情小说？ - 好啦 二流的情色书刊
- Great novels?     - Fine. Mediocre porn.
- 盖文米丘办公室   - 瑞秋葛林办公室
- Gavin Mitchell's office.     - Rachel Green's office.
电话给我
Give me that phone.
哈罗 我是瑞秋葛林 可以为您效劳吗？
Hello, this is Rachel Green. How can I help you?
好的 我会把电话传给你儿子
Uh-huh. Okay, then. I'll pass you back to your son.
妈 不是 她只是我的秘书
Hey, Mom. No, that's just my secretary.
对不起 盖文 我有个问题必须要问你
Um, excuse me, Gavin. I have a question I need to ask you.
妈 我再回电给你 是的
Mom, I'll call you later. Yeah.
- 怎样？ - 如果你那么喜欢看屁股…
- Yes?     - If you like looking at butts so much...
你何不自己去照镜子呢？
why don't you just go look in a mirror?
感谢上帝 你终于说了
Thank God you finally said that.
三个小时前我就看到 你写在笔记本上了
I saw you make a note on your pad three hours ago.
- 天啊 我真的惹你厌 是不是？ - 喔 不 拜托…
- Man, I really bug you. Don't I?     - Oh, no. Please...
我根本不在乎你 更别提讨厌你
I don't care about you enough to bug me.
事实上 从现在开始 我会表现得很有格调
In fact, from now on, I'm going to take the high road...
而且我会对你非常好 妈妈的乖宝宝…
and I'm going to be very, very nice to you, you mama's boy...
从现在开始
starting right now.
- 嘿 瑞秋   - 嗨
- Hey, Rach.     - Hi.
- 准备好要吃生日午餐了吗？ - 好了
- Ready for your birthday lunch?     - I am.
但是首先 摩妮卡 我想要介绍你认识…
But first, Monica, I would like to introduce you...
我非常能干的同事 而且更重要的是…
to my very talented colleague and more importantly...
我的好朋友 盖文米丘
my wonderful friend, Gavin Mitchell.
- 幸会   - 幸会
- Pleased to meet you.     - Pleased to meet you.
你会来参加瑞秋的派对吗？
Are you coming to Rachel's party?
喔 不不不不 盖文没有办法 他已经有计划了
Oh, no, no, no. Gavin can't. He already has plans...
应该是要去看他妈妈
most likely with his mother.
我不介意 我可以取消 我不想错过我秘书的生日
I don't mind. I'll cancel them. I would never miss my secretary's birthday.
为什么你要邀请他？ 我无法忍受那个男的
Why did you invite him? I can't stand that guy.
- 你看起来跟他很好啊   - 我是装出来的
- You were being so nice to him.     - I was faking it.
你难道看不出来我是装的吗？
Can't you tell when I'm being fake?
嘿 菲利浦先生 很好看的西装
Hey, Mr. Phillips. Nice suit.
- 抓到了 真是好假   - 嘘
- Right there. That was so fake!     - Shh!
嗨
Oh, hi.
我真不敢相信 你邀请了盖文
I still can't believe you invited Gavin.
他是我最不想见到的人
I mean, he is just the last person I want to see.
安排派对的事 不用跟我客气 我很高兴你喜欢
You're welcome for the party. I'm glad you're having a good time.
我希望他不要出现 他当然不会 他讨厌我
God, I hope he doesn't show up. Of course he's not gonna show up, the guy hates me.
- 是吗？ - 什么？
- Does he?     - What?
或许他一直惹你生气 是因为喜欢你
Maybe he keeps bothering you so much because he likes you.
就像在小学一年级的时候 史基蓝吉会推我…
It's like in first grade when Skippy Lange would push me...
其实是因为他在暗恋我
because he secretly had a crush on me.
摩妮卡 你以为史基喜欢你吗？
Oh, Monica, you think Skippy liked you?
亲爱的 所有的男生都在打赌 看他是不是有办法推倒你
Honey, all those boys had a bet to see if he could knock you over.
- 她睡了 我带她回去   - 好的 谢谢
- She's out. I'm gonna take her home.     - Oh, okay. Thank you.
再见 甜
Bye, sweetheart.
你有在她身上看到 那些男人看到的东西吗？
Do you see what all the guys see in her?
不会想要踢她下床的
Wouldn't kick her out of bed.
我不可以再喝伏特加了
No more vodka for me.
嘿 瑞秋 现在可以 唱生日快乐歌了吗？
Hey, Rach. So can I sing "Happy Birthday" to you now?
- 当然可以   - 好的
- Yeah, sure.     - Oh. All right.
祝你生…
Happy birth...
待会见
See you later.
瑞秋 有人送你鞋子
Hey, Rach. Somebody got you shoes.
给我看
Give me.
- 哇哇 我的天啊   - 小心 小心
- Wow. Wow. Oh, my God!     - Careful! Careful!
这些是我的老鼠宝宝
These are my rat babies!
是啊 我们现在有老鼠宝宝了
Yeah. We have rat babies now.
你带老鼠来参加我的生日派对？
Oh, you brought rats to my birthday party?
我感觉像是中风一样
So this is what a stroke feels like.
我必须要带着他们 我们杀了他们的妈
Well, I had to bring them. We killed their mother.
他们现在是我们的责任了
They're our responsibility now.
你知道的 他们需要一直被照顾
You know, they require constant care.
你应该知道的 你自己也是母亲
You should know that, Rachel, you're a mother.
你把我女儿跟一只老鼠做比较？
Are you comparing my daughter to a rat?
不 是七只
No. Seven rats.
我们应该带他们回家了 他们需要吃东西了
I think we should take them home. We need to feed them.
你因为要照顾这盒老鼠 而离开我的派对？
Wait, you're gonna leave my party to take care of a box of rats?
嗯 我很抱歉 瑞秋 但是我不像你 好吗？
Well, I'm sorry, Rachel, but I'm not like you. Okay?
不是每个人都请得起帮手的
Not everyone can afford help.
嘿 乔伊跟莫莉去哪了？
Hey, where the hell are Joey and Molly?
我要你看住他们的
I asked you to watch them.
我很抱歉 我有点分心了
I'm sorry. I got a little preoccupied.
听着 我们要在发生事情前阻止他们
Look, we have to stop them before something happens.
我会跟随你的 大哥
Right behind you, big guy.
所以你瞧 莫莉 人们不了解…
So you see, Molly, what people don't understand...
演戏是一种纪律 是很辛苦的工作
is that acting is a discipline. It takes a lot of hard work.
- 所以你是在哪里学的？ - 我没有上大学
- So where'd you study?     - Oh, I didn't go to college.
- 那 是从哪里学会演戏的呢？ - 莫莉 演戏不是学来的
- No, where'd you study acting?     - Molly, people don't study acting.
莫莉 可以让我们谈几分钟吗？
Molly, uh, do you mind giving us just a minute?
- 当然 我去看艾玛   - 谢谢
- Sure. I'll go check on Emma.     - Thanks.
马僮就不能得到公主吗？
Will the stable boy never get the princess?
你以为你是在做什么？ 在我家沙发上跟她做爱？
What do you think you were gonna do, have sex with her here on my couch?
不 沙发皮会黏住我的屁股
No. The leather sticks to my ass.
这实在不公平 你凭什么认为 我会跟她上床…
This isn't fair. What makes you think I'm gonna sleep with her...
然后就抛弃她呢？
and then blow her off, huh?
你们难道不能敞开心胸接受 或许我是真的喜欢她…
Can't you guys open your minds to the possibility that I actually like her...
而且要的是真感情？
and might want something real?
听着 事情是自从瑞秋之后 我就没有对任何人有过这种感觉了
Look, the truth is I haven't felt this way about anyone since Rachel.
好吗？我以为我不能再爱人了
Okay? I didn't think I could ever love again.
- 少来了   - 乔伊
- Come on.     - Joe.
嗨 莫莉在吗？
Hi. Is Molly here?
在 请进 莫莉？
Uh, yeah, yeah. Come on in. Molly?
- 嘿 各位 这位是塔比莎   - 嘿
- Hey. Guys, this is Tabitha.     - Hey.
- 明天见   - 好的
- I'll see you tomorrow.     - Okay.
嗯 乔伊 我猜我们没事了
Uh, well, Joey, I guess we have no problem.
这就像是美梦成真
It's like my favorite fairy tale come true.
公主 马僮跟女同性恋
The princess, the stable boy and the lesbian.
好了 你先泡牛奶
Okay. Okay, you start preparing the formula...
我去换盒子
and I'll start changing the box.
然后就送他们上床睡觉
And then we gotta put them straight to bed.
为什么要让我们的爱情生活…
When did we become one of those couples...
环绕着老鼠呢？
whose lives revolve around their rats?
你知道吗？他们现在是我们的责任了
Well, you know what? They're our responsibility now.
好的 这些老鼠是我们的责任
Okay, fine. These rats are our responsibility.
要是他们交配后 变成上百只呢？
What happens when they mate and there are hundreds?
交配？他们是兄弟姐妹耶
Mate? They're all brothers and sisters.
是啊 但是对老鼠可不是问题
Yeah, uh, not such a problem with rats.
他们是"爱上谁就上谁"的那种
No, they're more of a "love the one you're with" kind of animal.
才不 真的吗？
No. Really?
喔…不要搞你姐姐啦
Oh, my... Get off your sister! Ew.
我的天 我们该怎么办呢？
Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
- 我们有七只老鼠   - 嗯
- The... We have seven rats.     - Uh-huh.
如果七只老鼠的每一只…
So, what if each of them has seven rats...
都再生七只 那就是…
and then each of those have seven rats? That's like...
我不会算数学
That's math I can't even do.
我们该怎么办呢？
What are we gonna do?
嗯 我知道这听起来很疯狂…
Well, I know this is gonna sound crazy...
但我们可以不让这盒老鼠 毁了我们的生活
but we could not let the box of rats ruin our lives.
是啊 好吧 我想你说的对
Yeah, okay. I guess you're right.
好了 我们必须要送走他们
All right, so we should just give them away.
但要送给有小孩 还有低脂饼干的好人家
But to nice families with children and reduced-fat Wheat Thins.
那些是霸柏最喜欢的
Those were Bob's favorites.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
- 你一定认为我疯了   - 不 我觉得你很善良
- You must think I'm crazy.     - No, I think you're sweet.
那好
Good.
这真是很难
This is just so hard.
好难割舍
It's hard for me to let them go.
我猜这让我联想起很多柱事
I guess it just brings back memories, you know...
就像我怀了我弟的三胞胎 最后还是必须送回给他们养
from when I gave birth to my brother's triplets and I had to give them up.
我没有告诉过你那件事吗？
I haven't told you about that yet, have I?
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
谢谢你帮我办派对 亲爱的 我应该帮你打扫吗？
Thanks for the party, honey. Should I help you clean up?
不要 你的派对结束了 现在换我的
No way. You had your party. Now I have mine.
- 一切还好吧   - 每次生日结束时…
- Is everything all right?     - I just get bummed...
都会觉得有点难过
when my birthday's over.
至少有一件事值得你高兴
Well, at least you have one thing to be happy about.
- 嗯？ - 你办公室那个浑蛋盖文…
- Mm?     - That jerk, Gavin, from your office...
- 没有来   - 哈啊
- didn't show up.     - Ah.
是啊 他好讨厌哦
Yeah, I hate him.
我们不是在说你 我们…
We weren't talking about you. We were...
好吧 来不及转了 算了
No. No way to recover. No. Okay.
－一定很好玩   - 嗯 是的
- Fun party.     - Well, it was.
你都错过了 因为你出现在…
And you would have seen it if you didn't show up at...
九点半？天啊 这派对糟透了
Nine-thirty? God. Ugh, this party was lame.
再一次 不用客气
Again, you're welcome.
听着 我只是要给你这个就走人
Look, I'll just give you this and go.
你买礼物给我 为什么？
Oh, you bought me a present. Why?
让我解释一下生日派对 是怎样的情况 通常有礼物…
Let me explain how birthday parties usually work. There are presents...
有蛋糕 或许还有第四个或第五个人
and a cake, perhaps a fourth or fifth person.
好的 我…
Okay, I, uh...
我送礼物给你 弥补一下我对你的恶劣
I got you the present to make up for being such a jerk to you.
嗯 好的 真好 而且你还写了卡片
Aw. Well, okay. Well, that's very nice. And you wrote a card.
- "盖文赠"   - 肺腑之言
- "From Gavin."     - I really mean it.
噢
Oh. Oh.
很美耶
Oh, it's beautiful.
- 如果你不介意…让我来   - 不会
- If you don't mind? Let me.     - No.
谁知道呢 非常合适
Well, what do you know, it fits.
瞧 盖文 你是可以当个好男人的
See, Gavin. You're capable of being a nice guy.
为什么你要刁难我呢？
Why do you give me such a hard time?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
摩妮卡好像认为 是因为你对我有感觉
Well, Monica seems to think it's because you have feelings for me.
我是对你有感觉
I do have feelings for you.
- 真的吗？ - 是的 我觉得你很烦人
- You do?     - Yes. I feel that you're a little annoying.
为什么？盖文 为什么？
See, why? Gavin, why?
就在我要对你改观的时候 你就…
Right when I'm about to change my opinion of you, you go and you...
你就这样做了
And you do that.
起先我很害怕 怕的不知所措
First I was afraid, I was petrified
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
嘿 听着 我有东西忘了带走
Listen, um, I think I left something here.
是有人忘了这个 是你的吗？
Oh. Uh, well, somebody left this. Is this yours?
不是 但是我蛮喜欢的
Oh. No, but I like it.
不是 有一只老鼠宝宝我忘了带走
No, I think I left one of my rat babies.
没 我没有看到 但是如果有 我会让你知道
Oh. Uh, well, no. I haven't seen it, but if I do, I'll let you know.
老鼠宝宝 老鼠宝宝 老鼠宝宝
Aah! Rat baby! Rat baby! Rat baby! Rat baby!
或许就是他
Maybe that's him.